# Logan Smiley

## Web Designer

#### Contact

2249 Canterbury Dr. Mechanicsburg, PA 17055 United States 717-877-6632 Ismiley2030@gmail.com

#### Soft Skills

- Communication skills digitally, in person, and via phone
- Time management and organization skills
- Strong work ethic

#### **Hard Skills**

- HTML5 and CSS3 proficiency
- CMS knowledge specifically WordPress.com
- UI/UX experience in creating compelling layouts
- Adobe Illustrator experience along with other Adobe products.

#### Education

## Harrisburg Area Community College

Associates in Web Design and
Development
GPA 4.0 Highest Honors
Dean's List 2019-2021

#### **Achievements**

- Member of the PHI THETA KAPPA since 2020
- Dean's List 2019-2021
- Recognition of high-quality product photography from Hasbro 2019

#### **Key Skills**

# HTML & CSS Logo Design and high-fidelity prototypes Social media account management

#### **Experience**

- House sitting 2016-2021: Tasks included ensuring the home was secure overnight, retrieving mail, caring for various other household activities.
- Pet sitting 2016-2021: Tasks included feeding fish on daily basis, giving medication to pets daily, providing dogs and cat with clean water and fresh food, cleaning up after pets, feeding birds, dog sitting, and cat sitting.
- Created the updated Mechanicsburg Museum site. 2021.

#### References

Available upon request.

### Biography

My name is Logan Smiley. I graduated from Harrisburg Area Community College with a 4.0 GPA earning my Associate in Applied Sciences in Web Design and Development. I am a member of Phi Theta Kappa as well as being on the Dean's List from 2019-2021. My interest and principles are web design. I appreciate seeing all the elements of a site coming together such as images, text, and color palettes. I honed my skills in selecting typefaces, choosing appealing colors, and compelling photos and graphics. I spent three years learning how to use HTML and CSS effectively. I acquired some JavaScript experience as well. I also have knowledge of Wordpress.com and a basic understanding of Wordpress.org.

I enjoy helping people achieve their goals and one way to do that is by listening to what they want to accomplish. I can patiently listen and speak with clients, understanding that working with clients and assessing their needs is the best way to help them receive a website that will serve their business. This skill is beneficial as it allows me to better connect with people who are looking to establish an online presence for themselves or their business. I also have a passion for design and enjoy choosing compelling color schemes and creating a website that is as useful as it is interesting to view. Photography is a hobby I enjoy so I understand proper compositions in photography. My whole life I have had a passion for creativity and loved cartoon animation, video game design, and cinematography. Web design allows me to create something that would benefit others and allow them to make their unique voice heard on the internet which appealed to me, as I always wanted to do work that helped people in some capacity, and with web design, I can do just that.

To contact me you can message or follow me on LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/logan-smiley-767947190">https://www.linkedin.com/in/logan-smiley-767947190</a>. I am available also at my email address <a href="mailto:lsmiley2030@gmail.com">lsmiley2030@gmail.com</a>. My phone number is 717-877-6632 if you prefer to call or text.